making lilac tea is a treat that I look
forward to all year i watch with
anticipation waiting for when the blooms
are just ready for harvesting we have an
abundance of herbs and flowers available
to us that can be made into delicious
tea you can usually grow your own herbs
and flowers from seed but you can also
purchase them at your local nursery
[Music]
separating the sweet blossoms from the
more bitter stems is a time-consuming
process I often think of it as a sort of
labor a meditation in teaching me how to
be patient and thoughtful and in the
present
after the tea is brewed for a few
minutes I usually add something to give
the cup a little bit of sweetness
the first sip of tea is always the most
satisfying I love the taste and smell it
is always worth the effort to put love
and patience into everything you do the
end result is that much better
[Music]
of course there's nothing like a freshly
brewed cup of tea to inspire your
creativity I always find myself painting
with a cup next to my hand I'll see you
guys next time I upload videos every
Wednesday if you enjoyed this consider
subscribing thank you